gadgetsguru.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy of www.gadgetsguru.com

Customers are asked to provide certain information when they sign up for our Services such as name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member’s account (such as billing and collections). 

We use registration information to contact you in a variety of ways. We may send you offer through email, phone or regular mail of Gadgets Guru products and services. 

We store your information in a secure location. While we encourage you to take advantage of our Gadgets Guru personalized services, you can use most of our services without registering your information with us. You can change your information at any time by editing your profile in Gadgets Guru. 

We will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless we have your permission, special circumstances such as compliance with legal authorities, requires disclosure. We will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Gadgetsguru cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Regards,  
**Gadgets Guru.com**
